flutterwave.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Flutterwave

## Flutterwave Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes your privacy rights regarding how and when we collect, use, store, share and protect your information across our website, APIs, applications, email notifications and tools regardless of how you use or access them.

When this policy mentions “we,” “us,” or “our,” it refers to the controller of your information under this policy. If you live in Nigeria, the data controller responsible for your information is Flutterwave Technology Solutions Limited with its registered office at, 19, Olubunmi Rotimi Street, Lekki Phase One, Lagos, Nigeria and if you live outside Nigeria, the data controller responsible for your information is Flutterwave Inc. with its registered office at 1323 Columbus Avenue, San Francisco, CA 94133, USA.

Despite this, you alone control and are responsible for any and every information provided to us through the use of our services as provided in the Terms of Service.

Notwithstanding which country you live in, when using any of our services, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage, disclosure, and use of your information in Nigeria and any other country we operate as described in this privacy policy. This includes any information you choose to provide that is deemed sensitive under applicable law.

We respect the privacy of our online visitors and registered users and we will take reasonable steps to protect your information.

It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.

## What We Do to Information Collected

**Personal Information**

Upon registration, we collect personal information which you voluntarily provided by lawful means. We collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling the purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes.

This refers to the personal information you submit when you register (e.g., email address, company name, password, bank account number, etc.) it may also include anonymous information that is linked to you, for example, your IP Address. It should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

The following lists what we use your personal information for. These may be updated from time to time.

i. To provide you with access to our service.  
ii. To verify the information provided.  
iii. To prevent, detect and manage any illegal and fraudulent activity.  
iv. To improve our services to you.  
v. To address any inappropriate use of our services.  
vi. To update our website layout, database and content.  
vii. To target advertisements, newsletter and service updates

viii. Resolve disputes that may occur.

Additional personal information may be gotten from third party applications and other identification/verification services. For example, from your financial institution.

Once you begin to use our services, we keep all records of your transactions and we will not share or disclose your personal information with a third party without your consent.

**Web Visitors**

We do not collect information to web visitors. We may however collect non-personally-identifiable-information to enable us target advertisements to you, monitor and improve our website and services. This too, will not be shared or disclosed to third parties without your consent.

**Protecting Your Information**

We will protect your personal information by using global security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as against any unauthorized access, risk of loss, disclosure, copying, misuse or modification.

Other security measures include but not limited to, firewall, data encryption and granting access only to employees in order to fulfil their job responsibilities.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**Cookies**

Like many other websites, we use cookies to identify you as a user and to customize and improve our services. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer or mobile device. It enables us to remember your account log-in information, IP addresses, web traffic, number of times you visit, date and time of visits.

Some browsers may automatically accept cookies while some can be modified to decline cookies or alert you when a website wants to place a cookie on your computer. If you do choose to disable cookies, it may limit your ability to use our website.

**Data Storage**

We will only retain personal information on our servers for as long as an account is active. Once an account has been deactivated, your information is stored on our servers for as long as necessarily obligated by law.

This policy may change from time to time at our sole discretion.

_Last updated: 1st_ September, _2017_
